Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VII. Minutes, 1935-39, 1957-81
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VII. Minutes
1935-39, 1957-81
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s7
9.25 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
This series consists of minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, Association of Planned Parenthood Physicians, National Medical Committee, International Planned Parenthood Federation, and annual membership. It also includes annual reports. This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This series consists of minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee, Association of Planned Parenthood Physicians, National Medical Committee, International Planned Parenthood Federation, and annual membership. It also includes annual reports. The series includes microfilm, audiotape, and typed transcripts.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES VII. MINUTES
  - Annual Reports
    - 1975-78 (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
    - 1954-74 (Box 101, Folder 3-11)
    - Birth Control Federation of America 1935-39 (Box 101, Folder 12-13)
    - 1961 Income, Reported by Affiliates in Omnibus and Fund Raising, Reports, Turning Point, Annual Report, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 1962 Income, Reported by Affiliates in Omnibus and Fund Raising, Reports, Annual Report, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - 1962 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Work File 1960 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Transition 1957 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Looking Up 1958 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Breakthrough 1959 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 1963 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - [Was labeled: Annual Membership Meeting, Nov. 15-16, 1960. Actually contains document reading: Proceedings of the Panel Discussion on, "Education for Marriage in Your Community," May 3, 1956.] (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Updated Reprints List and Bibliography, 1974, Guttmacher Publication List 1962-66 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Reprints, AFG 1968-69, [Box 101 continued in SERIES IX: GUTTMACHER; boxes 102-195 are SERIES III: PUBLICATIONS through SERIES VI: REGIONS] (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Membership Meeting, October 2, 1980, Denver, Colorado, 1980 CLOSED (Box 196, Folder 2-3)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, December 5-6, 1980, New York, New York, 1980 (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, January 23-24, 1981, Washington, D.C., 1980 (Box 196, Folder 6-8)
  - Transcripts, Executive Committee Meeting
    - Oct. 14, 19778:00 A.M.-10:00 A.M. (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - July 22, 1977Afternoon Session (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Jan. 28, 1977 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts
    - International Convocation on the World Population Crisis, June 19-20, 1974, undated (Box 196, Folder 12-13)
    - Conference of Negro Physicians on PPWP 1968 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Margaret Sanger Centennial, Feb. 14, 1979 (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, National Medical Committee Meeting
    - Wednesday, January 31, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 16-18)
    - Wednesday, March 28, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 19-20)
    - Wednesday, May 30, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Wednesday, September 26, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Wednesday, November 28, 1973 (Box 196, Folder 23)
  - Reel-to-reel recordings of Board Meeting, Feb. 20, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 24)
  - List of Convention Sessions on Audio Cassettes, Annual Meeting, Oct. 22-28, 1978, San Diego, CA, 1978 (Box 196, Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, Cassettes, List and Record of Borrowers 1976 (Box 196, Folder 26)
  - Annual Meeting, Convention, Session on Audio Cassettes, List and Ordering Information 1978 (Box 196, Folder 27)
  - Cassettes-1976 Convention (Box 196)
  - Tapes
    - Alan F. Guttmacher, Memorial Service, April 18, 1974, Caspary Auditorium, Rockefeller University, #1-2, 1974 (Box 197)
    - Dr. AFG tape made for WFMB Station in Indianapolis, Indiana re: Population Danger, March 1966 (Box 197)
    - Dr. Stone, Sex Lecture #1 of 1, Feb. 11, 1958 (Box 197)
    - Board of Directors 1978 (Box 197)
    - Membership Meeting 1978 (Box 197)
    - Membership Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting 1978 (Box 197)
  - Microfilm
    - Planned Parenthood Transcripts, Roll #1, Board of Directors Meeting 1966-72 (Box 197)
    - Planned Parenthood, Annual Membership Meeting Minutes, May 1956-Oct. 1972 (Box 197)
    - Role No. 6, pre-1967 (Box 197)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, October 1, 1980Denver, Colorado (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership Meeting, 2:30 P.M., Houston, Texas 1979 (Box 197, Folder 3-4)
  - Transcripts, Annual Membership Meeting
    - Oct. 28, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Oct. 27, 1978 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - 10/15/779:00 A.M. (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - 10/14/772:00 P.M. (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - 10/30/76 (Box 197, Folder 9-10)
    - Oct. 19, 1974 (Box 197, Folder 11-12)
    - October 27, 1973 (Box 197, Folder 13-14)
  - Transcripts, Board of Directors Meetings
    - 1/26/80San Antonio, Texas (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
    - 11/16/798:30 A.M., Houston, Texas (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - June 1-2, 1979New York, N.Y. (Box 198, Folder 4-5)
    - 6/1/79Joint Session, Friday 1:45 P.M., N.Y.C. (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Feb. 9-10, 1979Washington, D.C. (Box 198, Folder 7-8)
    - October 27-28, 1978Saturday, San Diego, California (Box 198, Folder 9-11)
    - May 30-31, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 12-13)
    - June 3, 1978New York City (Box 198, Folder 14-15)
    - October 14-15, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 16-17)
    - June 3-4, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 18-19)
    - Jan. 29, 19778:30 A.M., Albuquerque, NM (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Jan. 28, 19772:30-6:00 P.M., Albuquerque, NM (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Oct. 29-30, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
    - June 4-5, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
    - Jan. 30-31, 1976 (Box 199, Folder 6-7)
    - Oct. 21-22, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 8-9)
    - 5/31/75, Saturday Morning and Afternoon Sessions, 1975 (Box 199, Folder 10-11)
    - 5/30/75 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - 10/18/742:30 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - June 1, 1974, Afternoon Session and Luncheon Meeting, Speaker Edward P. Morgan, 1974 (Box 199, Folder 14-15)
    - June 1-May 31, 1974 (Box 199, Folder 16-17)
    - Feb. 23, 19749:00 A.M.-5:00 P.M. (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Friday, Oct. 26, 19732:00-6:00 P.M. (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - May 22-23, 1973 (Box 200, Folder 1-3)
    - Feb. 16-17, 1973 and unedited (Box 200, Folder 4-5)
  - Bylaws and Constitution, Certificate Incorporation - APPP
    - Meetings, Roosevelt Hotel, New York City 1964 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 'Past,' 1963-65 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Budget 1964-68 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - M-8725 Sobrero's Memo, re: New Affiliations of Clinicians 1964 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Publication, re: Checks from Pharmaceutical Cos. 1964-65 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Association of P.P. Physicians [APPP]
    - Journal, "Advances in Planned Parenthood"
      - 1971-74 (Box 200, Folder 11)
      - 1977-80 (Box 200)
    - Proposed Amendments to Constitution and Bylaws
      - 1973 (Box 200, Folder 12)
      - 1977 (Box 200)
    - Medical Dept., General Correspondence 1969-72 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Financial
      - 1972-1974 (Box 200, Folder 14)
      - 1975-80 (Box 200)
  - Medical Department, APPP
    - General, Mimeos, Memos 1970 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, The Alan F. Guttmacher, M.D. Medical Lectureship
      - 1972-73 (Box 200, Folder 16)
      - 1977 (Box 200)
    - Membership Roster Index
      - 1971 (Box 200, Folder 17)
      - 1978-80, undated (Box 200)
  - APPP, Membership List 1964-68 (Box 200, Folder 18)
  - APPP
    - Medical Dept., Minutes
      - 1968-72 (Box 200, Folder 19)
      - 1978 (Box 200)
    - Nominating Committee 1965-68 (Box 200, Folder 20-21)
    - Post Graduate Day in Family Planning Services and Research, 4/5/72 (Box 200, Folder 22)
  - APPP, Postgraduate Program, Oct. 11, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 23)
  - AAPPP
    - Progress Report 1972 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Questionnaires, Medical Dept. 1977 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Reconvened Meeting, Mexico City, April 14-16, 1973 (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - Representation to Govt. Officials 1971 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - Medical Department, Report: Future Directions of AAPPP 1972 (Box 200, Folder 28)
  - APPP, Resolutions 1973-74 (Box 200, Folder 29)
  - APPP, Annual Meeting
    - Denver, Colorado 1980 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Hilton Hotel, Philadelphia, PA, 10/12, 1979 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - San Diego, CA 1978 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - Atlanta 1977 10/12-16 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - Papers: Abortion 1977 (Box 200, Folder 34)
    - Oct. 12-13, 1977 (Box 200, Folder 35)
    - Papers
      - Miscellaneous 1977 (Box 200, Folder 36)
      - Sterilization 1977 (Box 200, Folder 37)
  - APPP, Annual Meeting, Miami Beach, FL., 11/10-12, 1976 (Box 200, Folder 38)
  - APPP
    - 13th Annual Meeting
      - Correspondence: General, April 16-17, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 39)
      - Los Angeles, 4/17-18, Papers, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 40)
    - Annual Meeting Press Releases 1975 (Box 200, Folder 41)
    - Postgraduate Program, April 16, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 42)
    - 13th Annual Scientific Meeting, Los Angeles, California, 4/17-18/75 (Box 200, Folder 43)
    - 12th Annual Meeting, Memphis, Tenn., April 16-17, 1974
      - Correspondence (Box 200, Folder 44)
      - General (Box 200, Folder 45)
      - Papers (Box 200, Folder 46)
    - Postgraduate Program, Annual Meeting, April 15, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 47)
  - AAPPP
    - Seminar in Human Sexuality, Houston, Texas, April 11, 1973 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meetings
      - Houston, Texas, General, Mimeos, Memos 1973 (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Detroit, Michigan, General, Mimeos, Memos 1972 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - Kansas City, MO, Correspondence 1971 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - Boston, Mass.
        - Correspondence 1970 (Box 201, Folder 5)
        - General, Mimeos, Etc. 1970 (Box 201, Folder 6)
        - Papers 1970 (Box 201, Folder 7)
        - Press Releases 1970 (Box 201, Folder 8)
        - Resolutions 1970 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - San Francisco, Cal.
        - General 1969 (Box 201, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1969 (Box 201, Folder 11)
        - Nominating Committee 1969 (Box 201, Folder 12)
        - Press Releases 1969 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Business Meeting and President's Comments, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting San Antonio, Texas, Correspondence 1968 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Letters, Dr. Denniston, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, San Antonio, Texas, Miscellaneous 1968 (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - San Antonio Texas, Letters Following Meeting 1968 (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Pierson and Langmyhr, Papers, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 20)
    - Program Participants and Correspondence, San Antonio, Texas 1968 (Box 201, Folder 21)
    - San Antonio, Texas, Reimbursements 1968 (Box 201, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA., Correspondence 1967 (Box 201, Folder 23)
    - Exec. Committee, Minutes, April 2, 1967 (Box 201, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA., General and Mimeos 1967 (Box 201, Folder 25)
    - Proceedings of 5th, A Meeting, Atlanta, GA. 1967 (Box 201, Folder 26)
    - Atlanta Meeting Reimbursement 1967 (Box 201, Folder 27)
    - Atlanta Papers, circa 1967 (Box 201, Folder 28)
    - A Meeting, Denver, Colorado, Apr. 26-7, 1966
      - Correspondence (Box 201, Folder 29)
      - General, Mimeos 1966 (Box 201, Folder 30)
  - [OUT CARD: PP National: Physicians, Chicago Meeting, Papers 1965Complete Folder, Original Letters], [out] (Box 201, Folder 31)
  - American Association of Medical, Annual Meeting, Chicago, Ill.
    - Papers 1965 (Box 201, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence 1965 (Box 201, Folder 33)
    - General 1965 (Box 201, Folder 34)
  - AAPPP
    - Annual Meeting, Chicago, Ill.
      - Minutes 1965 (Box 201, Folder 35)
      - Dr. Perkin's Panel 1965 (Box 201, Folder 36)
  - Physicians, American Association of, A Meeting, Chicago, Ill., Releases 1965 (Box 201, Folder 37)
  - AAPPP Meeting, Chicago 1965 (Box 201, Folder 38)
  - Resolution, Gruening-Udall 1965 (Box 201, Folder 39)
  - AAPPP Meetings, Sheraton Hotel, Dallas 1964 (Box 201, Folder 40)
  - AAPPP Attendance, Dallas 1964 (Box 201, Folder 41)
  - IPPF Conferences
    - 6th International Conference
      - Correspondence
        - China Controversy 1958 (Box 201, Folder 42)
        - General 1958 (Box 201, Folder 43)
    - Lambeth Conference, London, England 1958 (Box 201, Folder 44)
    - Regional Conference, (Hague) Holland, Correspondence, General, May 1960 (Box 201, Folder 45)
    - 3rd Regional Conference (European-African Region), Warsaw, Poland, June 1962 (Box 201, Folder 46)
    - International Conferences, Meetings, Misc., General 1962 (Box 201, Folder 47)
    - 7th International Conference, Singapore, Misc. 1963 (Box 201, Folder 48)
  - "Economic Consequences of the Population Explosion," agenda 1962 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee minutes missing from microfilm 1965, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors agendas 1955-68 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Annual Membership meeting, minutes table of contents 1956-72 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Panel of PPFA-WPEC 1962 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Medical Committee meeting agenda 1956-72 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Affiliation Committee agendas 1958-65 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Ordering information for cassettes 1978 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm record 1956-72 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Symposia, meetings table of contents 1957-68 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Transcript, "A Forum on Man's Future," 1963 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Annual Membership meeting transcripts, table of contents 1959-71 (incomplete) (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Annual meeting transcripts 1961 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee meeting agendas 1966-70 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Affiliation committee meeting agendas 1966-70 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors meeting, table of contents 1955-61 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Medical Committee minutes 1963 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Medical Committee meeting minutes, missing from microfilm 1958-59, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, missing from microfilm 1948, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Indicies, Annual Membership meeting 1962-72 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Alan Guttmacher, IUD slides for Oliver Bird lecture 1964 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Alan Guttmacher Discussion, control of contraception, reel-to reel audiotape 1970 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Alan Guttmacher talk to students at Cornell, reel-to-reel audiotape 1970? [duplicate of 22?] (Box 132, Folder 23)
- SERIES VIII. FOREIGN
  - Proceedings of the Seventh Conference of the International Planned Parenthood Federation: Singapore, 1964
    - Papers presented 1963 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1962-63 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Western Hemisphere 4th Regional Conference, San Juan, Puerto Rico
    - Press conference 1964 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Papers and speeches 1964 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1963-64 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - International conferences, general correspondence 1964-65 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - 8th International Conference, Santiago Chile
    - 1966-68 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - General, miscellaneous, and speeches 1966-67 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Conference Bandung, "Getting More Out of the Mass Media," 1969 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - First International Medical & Scientific Congress, Sydney, Austrailia 1972 (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Fifth All India Conference on Family Planning, report of the proceedings 1964 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - 2nd Asian Population Conference, Tokyo 1972 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Foreign
    - A
      - Abortion in Foreign Countries 1952-68 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - General, Miscellaneous 1955-69 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Africa
        - Correspondence 1959-70 (Box 202, Folder 15-16)
        - Liberia, Family Planning Association of Liberia 1970-71 (Box 202, Folder 17)
        - Nigeria, IUDS 1969 (Box 202, Folder 18)
      - American, Samoa (United States Unincorporated Trust Territory), Correspondence
        - 1969-74 (Box 202, Folder 19)
        - 1977 (Box 202)
      - Asia 1952-62 (Box 202, Folder 20)
      - Australia
        - 1955-72 (Box 202, Folder 21)
        - 1978-79 (Box 202)
      - Austria 1955-61 (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - B
      - Bahamas 1953-60 (Box 202, Folder 21)
      - Belgium 1955-68 (Box 202, Folder 22)
      - Bermuda 1955-73 (Box 202, Folder 23)
      - Brazil
        - General, Correspondence
          - 1963-73 (Box 202, Folder 24)
          - 1975 (Box 202)
        - 11th International Conference of Social Work 1961-62 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - C
      - Canada
        - General, Correspondence
          - 1966-74 (Box 203, Folder 1)
          - 1975-79 (Box 203)
          - 1963-66 (Box 203, Folder 2-4)
        - The Family Planning Federation of Canada
          - 1971-74 (Box 203, Folder 5)
          - 1975 (Box 203)
        - Kitchener, Ontario, Kaufman, A.R., Parents' Information Bureau 1955-60, 1962-70 (Box 203, Folder 6)
        - Montreal
          - Family Planning Association 1964-72 (Box 203, Folder 7)
          - La Federation du Quebec pour le Planning du Naissances 1975-77 (Box 203, Folder 8)
        - Ottawa
          - Planned Parenthood Federation of Canada 1976-77 (Box 203, Folder 9)
          - PP, Correspondence 1969 (Box 203, Folder 10)
        - Toronto, PP Association
          - 1962-74 (Box 203, Folder 11)
          - 1977 (Box 203)
        - Requests for Information and Literature 1955-69 (Box 203, Folder 12)
        - Toronto, Cass Canfield, Speech, U.N. Association 1960-61 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Caribbean Area 1955-61 (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Central America
        - Costa Rica 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 15)
        - Guatemala 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 16)
        - Honduras 1954-67 (Box 203, Folder 17)
        - San Salvador 1955-68 (Box 203, Folder 18)
      - Ceylon, Correspondence 1958-68 (Box 203, Folder 19)
      - China
        - The People's Republic of China
          - Correspondence and General 1975-77 (Box 203, Folder 20)
          - Family Planning in the People's Republic of China
            - 1971-74 (Box 203, Folder 21)
            - 1975-77 (Box 203)
          - Visit of U.S. Family Planning Delegation 1977 (Box 203, Folder 22)
          - Mrs. Vineyard's Trip 1974 (Box 203, Folder 23)
        - Taiwan
          - Correspondence and General 1969 (Box 203, Folder 24)
          - MCH Center, Demonstration Project 1968-70 (Box 203, Folder 25)
          - Correspondence 1955-68 (Box 203, Folder 26)
          - MCH Demonstration Project, Reports 1970-72 (Box 203, Folder 27)
          - T. Paul Schultz: The Effectiveness of Family Planning in Taiwan 1969 (Box 203, Folder 28)
      - Cuba 1956, 1965-68 (Box 203, Folder 29)
    - Denmark 1955-69 (Box 203, Folder 30)
    - E
      - Egypt, Correspondence 1955-66 (Box 203, Folder 31)
      - England
        - Family Planning Association 1970-73 (Box 203, Folder 32)
        - Correspondence
          - 1964-72 (Box 203, Folder 33)
          - 1977 (Box 203)
          - 1959-63 (Box 203, Folder 34)
        - Field Reports 1956 (Box 203, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence, Searle and Co., Ltd. 1963-66 (Box 203, Folder 36)
    - F
      - Far East-European Trip, Dr. R. L. Day 1965-66 (Box 203, Folder 37)
      - Far East, Vietnam, Correspondence 1969-71 (Box 203, Folder 38)
      - Fiji 1963-74 (Box 203, Folder 39)
      - Finland 1955-65 (Box 203, Folder 40)
      - Formosa 1955-60 (Box 203, Folder 41)
      - France, Correspondence 1960-72 (Box 203, Folder 42-43)
    - G
      - Germany, Correspondence 1960-70 (Box 203, Folder 44-45)
      - Greece, Correspondence 1964 (Box 203, Folder 46)
      - Guam (United States Unincorporated Trust Territory), Correspondence
        - 1974 (Box 203, Folder 47)
        - 1975 (Box 203)
    - H
      - Haiti
        - 1956-74 (Box 203, Folder 48)
        - 1975 (Box 203)
      - Holland, Correspondence 1961-66 (Box 203, Folder 49)
      - Hong Kong 1955-69 (Box 203, Folder 50)
    - I
      - India
        - Orientation of Indian Students 1962-64 (Box 204, Folder 1)
        - Mrs. Indira Gandhi, Prime Minister of India, Trip to U.S. 1966 (Box 204, Folder 2)
        - Conference, Miscellaneous and Schedules 1968 (Box 204, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence
          - 1964-67 (Box 204, Folder 4)
          - 1968-74 (Box 204, Folder 5)
          - 1975, 1979 (Box 204)
          - 1961-63 (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - Indonesia 1958-72 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Iran 1955, 1964-70 (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Ireland 1955-56, 1958-72 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - Israel 1961-69 (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - Italy 1962-69 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Japan 1958-69 (Box 204, Folder 12-13)
    - Korea 1956-69 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - L
      - Latin America
        - 1964-66 (Box 204, Folder 15)
        - Latin American Seminar
          - 2nd Family Planning Orientation for Leaders 1963 (Box 204, Folder 16)
          - Programs, Miscellaneous 1962 (Box 204, Folder 17)
          - 1st Family Planning Orientation For Leaders 1962 (Box 204, Folder 18)
          - Publicity, News Clips 1962 (Box 204, Folder 19)
        - Ofelia Mendoza, Reports, Field Trips 1954-65 (Box 204, Folder 20)